[{"answer": "Well, I mean if you talk to Russian officials they insist that this is going to be the safest winter games ever.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "How seriously should we be taking it?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "So far so good.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "Are you psyched?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "Yesterday, we were doing processing and then we were traveling all morning.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "Does that stress you out?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "AIA SHIBUTAN: Yeah.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "Yeah?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "You know, hey everyone we're in Sochi.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "And any message you want to send back home?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "I have to say yes.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "I mean you've covered many events on your time, do you fell reasonably secure?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "Ivan Watson, thank you very much indeed.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "Piers?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "Airplanes, absolutely.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "Bob, if you were involved in the counterterrorist operation here, what would your biggest worry be now?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "I think they are serious about this.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "Is that indicative to your mind that they are really expecting something to happen or that is being ultra cautious?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "AER: Absolutely.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "I mean this is clearly something they're going to be serious about it, isn't it?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "I'm doing great, Piers.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "Winston, how are you?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Piers, I never like to tell the world what the Jamaican team go to do.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "Do you have any chance of getting a medal, do you think?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Yes they do give us the respect of course because we're from a tropical country.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "Do you slightly resent the fact that people don't perhaps give you the credit and the respect you guys deserve?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "What we do, we have lots of people here who loved us, you know, everyone here in the village they have -- there were so, you know, the polite for us, want to lend us uniforms, stuff like that and I'm -- for our uniform our baggage was left back in New York because our flight was delayed and because they had bad weather in New York and we have to reroute it to -- well in JFK we should have landed and we have to rerouted to Philadelphia.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "And if it doesn't turn up, what will you do?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "I've yet to hear from Usain.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "Has he been in touched to wish you guys luck?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "I am going to run for governor for the state of California.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "Seriously, what are you going to do?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "Yes, that's what it is.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "Is it simply jealousy that he's been number one for two decades?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "Jay, you know, this shows they're difficult, you know, you run a show.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "Yeah, he tried to be funny for everyone, he lost that edge deliberately, where is the truth?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "That the guy is still number one in the ratings?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "Let me -- arguably, the most -- one of the most successful stand ups in the history of ...", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "Why don't we (inaudible) and start over again?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "Beats me.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "Now, Mr. Grady (ph), for fun getaways, where can you get the best bang for your buck?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "Which was always his most important thing?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "Let's talk quickly about the Conan O'Brien Debacle (inaudible).", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "So that's your excuse?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "Am I wrong was he blamed?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "I mean, well that maybe he should step aside and just let Conan take the show, maybe it wasn't right to go back.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "I like Jay Leno.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "What do you make of Jay Leno?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "Well, of course, a lot of it is that.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Is it jealousy?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "About what Jerry said?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "Well, I think they, you know, when I was in the show, we had -- in my first year, it was Danitra Vance and Damon Wayans who are, you know, African-American, whatever.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "Should Saturday Night Live, John, of being almost forced into having a more diverse star than the way that they were by pressure from the media?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "Well, I think the day after the show goes off, he's flying to Florida with this little one nighters (ph).", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "What would you think about this?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "He's not part of the family, isn't he?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "I think he'll do another show somewhere else.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "So what do you think he'll do quickly?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "In fact, yes.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "If you are Jay Leno and you're 63 and you've had this incredible full time job for the last 22 years and suddenly you don't have it, a lot of people find that period in their lives really difficult to deal with?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "Well, he has to continue.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "What is the best way to navigate being out of a job like that?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "Are you really?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "You've never been hospitalized in your life?", "qSentId": 613}, {"answer": "Very rarely.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "Do you get colds, flu, stuff like that or not?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "You should come and spend a week with me at the Chopra Center for Wellbeing.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 626, "question": "Why can't I be like you, Deepak?", "qSentId": 625}, {"answer": "Piers, first of all, addiction is the number one disease of our civilization and directly or indirectly, it's connected to all the other major epidemics of our time, whether it is cardiovascular illness or sudden death or suicide or overdose.", "docId": "140206pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "What advice do you give to people, particularly like him, who've been addicts and then being clean for long time, but still wrestled with those demons?", "qSentId": 650}]